<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Machine Learning on SA Dev</title>
    <link>https://palikar.github.io/categories/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Machine Learning on SA Dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://palikar.github.io/categories/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes on learning Numpy</title>
      <link>https://palikar.github.io/posts/numpy_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://palikar.github.io/posts/numpy_notes/</guid>
      <description>My notes while reading this. More or less copy paste. Take with a grain of salt&amp;hellip;or sugar.

Abstract NumPy is a Python package. It stands for &amp;lsquo;Numerical Python&amp;rsquo;. It is a library consisting of multidimensional array objects and a collection of routines for processing of array. From the officials:
 NumPy is the fundamental package for scientific computing with Python. It contains among other things:
 a powerful N-dimensional array object sophisticated (broadcasting) functions tools for integrating C/C++ and Fortran code useful linear algebra, Fourier transform, and random number capabilities  Besides its obvious scientific uses, NumPy can also be used as an efficient multi-dimensional container of generic data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes on learning Pandas</title>
      <link>https://palikar.github.io/posts/pandas_notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://palikar.github.io/posts/pandas_notes/</guid>
      <description>For transparency sake - those are my notes while learning about pandas from this tutorial. At times this here is just copy paste from it, at other it&amp;rsquo;s my own thoughts and explanations. This is meant to be a condensed version of the tutorial more or less just for me. If you found it useful though&amp;hellip;.well, good for you, I guess.

Abstract Basic pandas is a Python package providing fast, flexible, and expressive data structures designed to make working with &amp;ldquo;relational Heterogeneous data&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;labeled&amp;rdquo; data both easy and intuitive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>