<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on SA Dev</title>
    <link>https://palikar.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on SA Dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://palikar.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Emacs windows resizing</title>
      <link>https://palikar.github.io/posts/emacs_framer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://palikar.github.io/posts/emacs_framer/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been introduced to the concept of a tiling windows manger. One key feature that caught my attention is how you can quickly resize your different windows and create your desired windows configuration with just a few executions of some keybindings. That got me wonder how it would really cool if I also have that in Emacs. I googled something like &amp;ldquo;resize emacs windows&amp;rdquo; but didn&amp;rsquo;t really (I didn&amp;rsquo;t want really) find package that can do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C&#43;&#43; Template Specialization</title>
      <link>https://palikar.github.io/posts/cpp_template_specialization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://palikar.github.io/posts/cpp_template_specialization/</guid>
      <description>Abstract C++ is awesome! I am starting stong here but it&amp;rsquo;s really is. When experienced (and crazy) enough one can implement everything and the same one can do it icredibaly efficient at run time(cuz who cares how much work does the compiler do for us, amirite?). I can rant about how c++ is the best and all of the great features of the language but for this article I would constraint myself to one partzicular(but rather big) - template metaprogramming!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github commits&#39; emails change</title>
      <link>https://palikar.github.io/posts/github_history_repair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://palikar.github.io/posts/github_history_repair/</guid>
      <description>Abstract You know that Contributions panel on your Github profile page. Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, developers these day take much pride when they can show their consistent work and progress of their own/forked repositories&amp;hellip;even when some of their commits are nothing more than a implementations of a single function. Said panel is clear indication to you, future employee or members of your &amp;lsquo;coding community&amp;rsquo; that you are pretty much a big deal with a good work ethic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>